Why don't you come in?
들어오지 그래?
I don't want to disturb you in chat
채팅을 방해하고 싶지 않아요
I brought you chicken rice
치킨라이스를 가져왔어
Can you bring something else next time?
다음에는 다른 것을 가져올 수 있나요?
Don't you like this?
당신은 이것을 좋아하지 않습니까?
The taste will change
맛이 바뀔거에요
how
어떻게
how's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
Or an ordinary person
아니면 평범한 사람
Either an expert
전문가라든가
Do you think
당신은 생각합니까?
Does she know your identity?
그 사람이 당신의 정체를 알고 있나요?
I hope so
나는 희망한다
worst degree
최악의 학위
you probably know everything
넌 아마 다 알고 있을 거야
So you still fell into the trap
그래서 당신은 여전히 ​​함정에 빠졌어요
Why do I feel this way?
왜 이런 느낌이 들까요?
you have a great plan
당신은 훌륭한 계획을 갖고 있어요
How is your leg injury?
다리 부상은 어때요?
Skin injuries are easy
피부상처가 쉽죠
you don't decide
당신은 결정하지 않습니다
Go to the hospital for examination
병원에 가서 검사를 받으세요
it's time
때가됐다
It's time to change medicine
약을 바꿀 시간이에요
your sudden interest
너의 갑작스러운 관심
I'm not used to this
난 이게 익숙하지 않아
Didn't you close the door?
문 안 닫았어?
past?
과거?
you should feel pain now
지금은 고통을 느껴야 해
presentable
표현 가능한
Don't get pregnant in front of me
내 앞에서 임신하지 마
Why?
왜?
I do not know you
난 당신을 몰라
you are so annoying
너 정말 짜증나
Don't you want to know?
알고 싶지 않으세요?
Huang Zicheng’s situation
황쯔청의 상황
Looks like he's having some problems
그 사람 뭔가 문제가 있는 것 같아
Yaoyao admitted it
야오야오가 인정했어
He said it was night fog
밤안개였다고 하더군요
always
언제나
Why
왜
She honestly confessed to Huang Zi
황자에게 솔직하게 고백한 그녀
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
I think Yaoyao is behind
내 생각엔 Yaoyao가 뒤쳐진 것 같아
This must be a hidden secret
이건 숨겨진 비밀임에 틀림없어
Why do you think so?
왜 그렇게 생각하시나요?
When I was at the Viking Hotel
바이킹 호텔에 있었을 때
I saw she met a boy
나는 그녀가 어떤 남자를 만나는 걸 봤어요
I checked
나는 확인했다
That young man’s name is Fang Lu
그 청년의 이름은 Fang Lu입니다.
Feng Lu
루펑
You didn't expect it?
기대하지 않았나요?
I just joined the group
방금 그룹에 가입했어요
They said you were looking for Chen Ting
Chen Ting을 찾고 있다고 하더군요
in her network
그녀의 네트워크에서
Fang Lu
팡 루
So I come to you
그래서 나는 당신에게 간다
Vice Mayor Fang Lu
팡루 부시장
Fang Yongping's son
팡용핑의 아들
How could Yaoyao know?
Yaoyao는 어떻게 알 수 있었습니까?
So I said behind Yaoyao's back
그래서 나는 야오야오의 뒤에서 말했다.
must have
가지고 있어야 한다
more secrets
더 많은 비밀
Can't let her go easily
그녀를 쉽게 보낼 수 없어
Fang Lu, Yao Yao, Chen Ting
팡루, 야오야오, 첸팅
relation
관계
Is he too?
그 사람도 그렇나요?
from the night fog
밤안개로부터
You can't make a decision now
지금은 결정을 내릴 수 없습니다.
It would be great if it was Fang Lu
팡루였다면 참 좋았을 텐데
easy to say
말하기 쉽다
what is he afraid of
그 사람은 무엇을 두려워하는가?
Ye Wu is not just colluding with Fang Lu
Ye Wu는 단지 Fang Lu와 공모한 것이 아닙니다.
Chen Ting
첸 팅
And the power is behind him
그리고 그 뒤에는 권력이 있다
I got you
나는 당신을 얻었다
this matter
이 문제
may be related
관련이있을 수 있습니다
Some government department officials
일부 정부 부처 관계자
According to relevant legal provisions
관련법령에 의거
Hotel of the month
이달의 호텔
signal tower
신호탑
is the opposite
반대다
Cross the line
선을 넘어
High level of construction
높은 수준의 건축
not built
지어지지 않은
How did Zhao Jun get it?
Zhao Jun은 어떻게 얻었습니까?
approval procedure
승인 절차
someone help him
누군가 그를 도와줘
Does Zhao Jun know that he didn’t build it?
Zhao Jun은 자신이 그것을 만들지 않았다는 것을 알고 있습니까?
He works in hotel development
그는 호텔 개발 분야에서 일한다
He must have known it wasn't built yet
그는 그것이 아직 지어지지 않았다는 것을 알았을 것입니다.
It’s not easy for Zhao Jun
Zhao Jun에게는 쉽지 않습니다.
approved
승인됨
behind this signal tower
이 신호탑 뒤에
This is a complex network of relationships
이것은 복잡한 관계망이다.
You are just like Zhao Jun
당신은 Zhao Jun과 같습니다
there are others
다른 사람들도 있어요
who copied
누가 복사했는가
we should
우리는해야한다
Clearly
분명히
Tianyang, you are responsible for this matter
Tianyang, 당신은 이 문제에 대한 책임이 있습니다
Understood
이해했다
Huang Zicheng’s temperament is also
황자성 성격도 그렇고
How is he now?
그는 지금은 어떤가요?
this time
이 시간
It was a big shock to him
그에게는 큰 충격이었다
Next let Huang Ziqing
다음으로 황자칭(Huang Ziqing)을 보자
Contact Yaoyao
야오야오에게 연락하기
and learn more about its hidden secrets
숨겨진 비밀에 대해 자세히 알아보세요.
amor
사랑
In order to recover as soon as possible
최대한 빨리 회복하기 위해서는
OK
좋아요
Mr. Chen
첸 씨
let me talk to him
그 사람이랑 얘기 좀 하자
Mind your limits
한계를 염두에 두세요
Actually you don’t have to come with me
사실 나랑 같이 갈 필요는 없어
I'll go alone
나 혼자 갈게
Safe Zone Huang Zicheng
안전지대 황쯔쳉
I thank you
감사합니다
You are very polite
당신은 매우 예의 바르다
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
How should I speak?
어떻게 말해야 하나요?
this is work
이건 일이야
this is normal
이건 정상이야
I'll treat you to dinner another day
다른 날 저녁 식사로 대접할게
Don't eat in bars
바에서 식사하지 마세요
Huang Zicheng and I have a date
황쯔청과 나는 데이트를 해요
I won't go with you
나는 당신과 함께 가지 않을 것입니다
no problem
괜찮아요
If your doctor tells you to stay in the hospital
의사가 병원에 ​​입원하라고 지시하는 경우
Everything is under the doctor's arrangement
모든 것은 의사의 지시에 따른다
What's the difference between you and me?
당신과 나 사이의 차이점은 무엇입니까?
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
Yaoyao is a spy
야오야오는 스파이다
That's how it feels
그 느낌이에요
of course not
당연히 아니지
in the past
과거에
country to me
나라는 나에게
for me
나를 위한
but this time
하지만 이번에는
When you're on a limited path
제한된 길에 있을 때
I saw Sister Shi
나는 시 자매를 보았다
at that moment
그 순간
This concept suddenly appeared
갑자기 이런 컨셉이 나오네요
It seems that I have become
된 것 같아요
I have confidence
나는 자신감을 갖고 있다
I won't be alone
나는 혼자가 아닐 것이다
It seems that I suddenly
아무래도 내가 갑자기
I know you
나는 당신을 알고
At work, persevere
직장에서는 인내심을 갖고
National Security
국가 안보
protect the integrity of the country
국가의 완전성을 보호하다
food is ready
음식이 준비됐어요
It's time to eat
이제 먹을 시간이다
I am coming
나는 온다
let's go
갑시다
honestly
솔직히
They are really cruel
정말 잔인해요
this is the first time
이번이 처음이야
when i face my real fears
내가 진짜 두려움에 직면했을 때
if you were me
당신이 나라면
i will kill them
내가 그들을 죽일 것이다
But Lao Huang is here too
그런데 라오황도 여기 있네
How can I get him involved?
어떻게 하면 그 사람을 참여시킬 수 있나요?
At that moment I was about to collapse
그 순간 나는 쓰러질 뻔했다
War is not a game
전쟁은 게임이 아니다
Cruelty is the truth
잔인함은 진실이다
Understood
이해했다
this place
여기
I brought Yaoyao here before
예전에 야오야오를 여기로 데려왔었는데
I'm thinking now
지금 생각 중이야
They may all be visible
모두 보일 수도 있습니다
Didn't you tell them?
그들에게 말하지 않았나요?
we start to intervene
우리가 개입하기 시작해요
I'm not that stupid
나 그렇게 멍청하진 않아
struggle
고심하다
Who reveals his or her identity first?
자신의 정체를 먼저 밝히는 사람은 누구일까요?
Who will lose?
누가 잃을 것인가?
our relationship
우리의 관계
at first
처음에는
About lies
거짓말에 대하여
No matter which side is revealed
어느 쪽이 드러나든 상관없어
The result will be very bad
결과가 매우 나쁠 것이다
What do you think of our relationship?
우리 관계에 대해 어떻게 생각하세요?
Will there be good results?
좋은 결과가 있을까요?
in battle
전투 중
Emotions are the victims
감정이 피해자다
The more you fall, the more dangerous you are
넘어질수록 위험해진다
Let me talk about feelings with you
당신과 감정에 대해 이야기하겠습니다
you're talking to me about work
너 지금 나한테 일 얘기하는 거야?
Brother, can you be more harmonious?
형님, 좀 더 조화롭게 지내실 수 있나요?
You know why I always tell you
내가 왜 항상 네게 말하는지 알잖아
Didn't you do a good job?
좋은 일을 하지 않았나요?
Do you know why
왜인지 아세요?
are you single
당신은 싱글인가요?
Are you quarreling?
당신은 말다툼을하고 있습니까?
Do you still feel uncomfortable?
아직도 불편함을 느끼시나요?
after everything
모든 것 후에
You were beaten because of me
나 때문에 너 맞았어
but you don't know
하지만 당신은 몰라요
What kind of person is she
그녀는 어떤 사람인가요?
Maybe act with you
어쩌면 당신과 함께 행동할 수도 있습니다
like a series
시리즈처럼
what do you like
당신은 무엇을 좋아하나요?
Only characters in this series
이 시리즈의 유일한 캐릭터
not an actor
배우가 아니다
she is always playing
그 사람은 항상 놀고 있어
your favorite character
당신이 가장 좋아하는 캐릭터
make
만들다
He makes you love her
그는 당신이 그녀를 사랑하게 만듭니다
maybe in this world
어쩌면 이 세상에
in this world
이 세상에서
This guy Yaoyao
이놈 야오야오
Even the name is fake
이름마저 가짜네
"Gao Tianyang."
"가오텐양."
i found you
내가 당신을 찾았어요
in the realm of private love
개인적인 사랑의 영역에서
you have great experience
당신은 훌륭한 경험을 가지고 있습니다
I believe
나는 믿는다
no one can help you
아무도 당신을 도울 수 없습니다
I can only endure it myself
나 혼자만 참을 수 있어
Since you have chosen
당신이 선택했기 때문에
this battle
이 전투
you have to overcome this difficulty
이 어려움을 극복해야 해
Do you think this is a sacrifice?
이것이 희생이라고 생각하십니까?
does it worth?
그만한 가치가 있나요?
in my eyes
내 눈에
this is not a sacrifice
이것은 희생이 아니다
You want me to play games like you
당신은 내가 당신처럼 게임을 하길 원해요
as a programmer
프로그래머로서
How much will you give me
얼마를 주실 건가요?
i don't want to do that
난 그러고 싶지 않아
I'm not interested
난 관심 없어
no motive
동기 없음
If you want me to be Duane
내가 Duane이 되길 원한다면
even if i have no money
나에게 돈이 없더라도
I'm willing to do this
나는 기꺼이 이것을 할 의향이 있다
even though
~ 일지라도
for him
그를 위해
I don't think it's a sacrifice
희생은 아닌 것 같아요
I can overcome it too
나도 이겨낼 수 있어
I can sacrifice for my country
조국을 위해 희생할 수 있다
but i don't believe it
하지만 나는 그것을 믿지 않는다
A person can give up
사람은 포기할 수 있다
his feelings
그의 감정
Humans are emotional animals
인간은 감정의 동물이다
I'm not saying give up on feelings
감정을 포기하라는 게 아니다
but give up freedom
하지만 자유를 포기하다
Give up your happiness and sadness
당신의 행복과 슬픔을 포기하세요
But you close yourself
하지만 당신은 자신을 닫습니다
Give up being an ordinary person
평범한 사람이기를 포기하세요
Guoan has not abandoned humanity
궈안은 인류를 버리지 않았다
This is not an abandonment of humanity
이것은 인류를 포기하는 것이 아니다
But control desire
그러나 욕망을 통제하라
you have to remind yourself
너는 스스로 상기시켜야 해
Don’t make the mistake of talking while drunk
술에 취해서 말하는 실수를 저지르지 마세요
you can't speak without restrictions
넌 제한 없이는 말할 수 없어
you can't relax
넌 긴장을 풀 수 없어
you can't do whatever you want
당신은 당신이 원하는 무엇이든 할 수 없습니다
Because the opponent is always in darkness
상대는 항상 어둠 속에 있기 때문에
in the darkness
어둠 속에서
hard
딱딱한
very difficult
매우 어렵다
"Gao Tianyang."
"가오텐양."
I sympathize with you
나는 당신에게 공감합니다
presentable
표현 가능한
You will get used to it
익숙해 질거야
i'm making fun of you
나는 당신을 놀리고 있어요
I didn't hear
나는 듣지 못했다
Understood
이해했다
this is not
이것은 아니다
I think of private workers
개인사업자 생각나네요
Don't you believe it?
믿을 수 없나요?
I can do it
난 할 수 있어
I trust you
나는 당신을 신뢰합니다
I just don't want to see
난 그냥 보고 싶지 않아
accept this pain
이 고통을 받아들여
You could have
당신은 가질 수 있습니다
You live a carefree life
당신은 평온한 삶을 살고 있습니다
Is not this contradictory?
이는 모순되지 않는가?
As long as you can overcome this pain
이 고통을 이겨낼 수만 있다면
you will become stronger
당신은 더 강해질 것입니다
So you think I can come back
그럼 내가 돌아올 수 있을 거라 생각하는 거지?
Continue to investigate Yaoyao
계속해서 야오야오를 조사하라
There is no murmur in his heart
그의 마음에는 불평이 없다.
no feeling
아무 느낌이 없다
At least don't let these feelings go away
적어도 이 감정이 사라지지는 않게 해주세요
affect your judgment
당신의 판단에 영향을 미치다
i will try my best
난 내 최선을 다할 것입니다
I don't try
나는 노력하지 않는다
but guaranteed
하지만 보장
Okay, I'll try my best to control it
알았어, 최선을 다해 통제할게
This is just the beginning
이건 시작에 불과해
there's still a long way to go
아직 갈 길이 멀다
I just hope you don't give up
포기하지 않길 바랄 뿐이야
Hello
안녕하세요
Tian Yang
양 티안
Zhao Jun did not show up
조준은 나타나지 않았다
appear in company
회사에 나타나다
Understood
이해했다
wait me back
기다려줘
eat quickly
빨리 먹어
It's cold
추워
eat more
더 드세요
Zhao Jun is on a business trip in the afternoon
조준은 오후에 출장 중
Maybe Homeland Security
아마도 국토안보부
Can't find it yet
아직 찾을 수 없습니다
This time it seems to be the National Security Bureau
이번에는 국가안전보위부인 것 같다.
he won't give up
그 사람은 포기하지 않을 거야
Planning Department
계획 부서
Do you have any questions
질문있으세요
The planning bureau can handle it
기획국에서 처리할 수 있어요
Someone will bear it
누군가는 참아주겠지
The most important thing now is Zhao Jun
지금 가장 중요한 것은 조준이다.
Can you withstand Guo An's investigation?
Guo An의 조사를 견딜 수 있습니까?
I know
알아요
As for Zhao Jun
자오쥔의 경우
I'll take care of it
내가 처리할게
I will try my best to make everything go smoothly
모든 일이 원활하게 진행될 수 있도록 최선을 다하겠습니다.
It ends here
여기서 끝
Now the Office of National Security
지금은 국가안보실
can you think of a way
방법을 생각해 줄 수 있어?
stop investigation
조사를 중단하다
I've gone beyond
나는 그것을 넘어섰다
Nature
자연
Where is the leadership?
리더십은 어디에 있습니까?
Mayor, you haven't left yet
시장님, 아직 떠나지 않으셨습니다
Enter.
입력하다.
close the door
문을 닫다
I heard there is
있다고 들었는데
Investigate illegal cases
불법 사건 수사
what happened
무슨 일이에요
Ono Hotel
오노 호텔
in the signal tower
시그널 타워에서
I found a camera at the top
꼭대기에서 카메라를 발견했어요
they knock on the door
그들은 문을 두드린다
Opposite the military base
군부대 맞은편
Who approved it?
누가 승인했나요?
Planning Department
계획 부서
Did you say hello?
안녕이라고 하셨나요?
stupid
멍청한
I really do not know
나는 정말로 모른다
they arrange cameras
그들은 카메라를 준비한다
They think the signal tower
그들은 신호탑을 생각한다
Have I found you?
내가 당신을 찾았나요?
No
아니요
Someone will be responsible for the planning office
기획실을 담당하는 사람이 있을 것입니다.
At most it's legal punishment
기껏해야 법적 처벌 수준
I'm scared now
지금은 무서워요
The National Security Bureau won't release him
국가안전보위국은 그를 석방하지 않을 것이다
The hotel owner’s name is Zhao Jun
호텔 주인 이름은 Zhao Jun입니다.
Now the Office of National Security
지금은 국가안보실
He started interrogating him
그는 그를 심문하기 시작했다
Do not communicate with the following people
다음과 같은 사람과는 연락하지 마세요
with these founders
이 창업자들과 함께
Things are different now
지금은 상황이 달라졌어
Yes
예
There is a problem with national security
국가안보에 문제가 있다
Can I solve the problem?
문제를 해결할 수 있나요?
Can be solved
해결 가능
allow
허용하다
go
가다
I'll ask later
나중에 물어볼게
Tian Yang
양 티안
We went to Zhaojun Company
우리는 Zhaojun 회사에 갔다
He didn't go to work all day
그 사람은 하루 종일 회사에 가지 않았어
The secretary said he was on a business trip
비서가 출장 중이라고 하더군요
Where did he go?
그는 어디로 갔습니까?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
Do you see it at home?
집에서도 보이나요?
Pony is watching over there
포니가 저기서 지켜보고 있어요
No one is back now
이제 아무도 돌아오지 않았어
Ask the second group to observe
두 번째 그룹에게 관찰하도록 요청하세요.
I'm going to the planning office tomorrow
내일 기획실에 갈 거야.
see what happens
무슨 일이 일어나는지 봐
Zhao Jun
조준
Once there is news
일단 소식이 있어요
notify me immediately
즉시 나에게 알려줘
Understood
이해했다
its strong
강하다
He went to the company again
그 사람 또 회사에 갔어요
Go to work first
먼저 일하러 가세요
Can I rest assured?
안심할 수 있나요?
national security office
국가안보실
This is not the tax office
여기는 세무서가 아니예요
tell me
말해 주세요
Is this dangerous?
이거 위험한가요?
Don't worry
괜찮아요
It's none of your business
너와는 상관 없어
at first
처음에는
It's not my turn yet
아직 내 차례가 아니야
you used my place
넌 내 집을 이용했지
Only build signal towers
신호탑만 건설하세요
besides it
게다가
I asked someone to approve it
다른 사람에게 승인을 요청했습니다.
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
if they ask me again
그들이 나에게 다시 묻는다면
i will tell the truth
나는 진실을 말할 것이다
National Security Office Thunder
국가안보실 썬더
I can not stand it any more
난 더 이상 참을 수 없어
I didn't ask you to bear it
참아달라고 한 게 아닌데
stay here for a few days
며칠 동안 여기 있어라
I'll take care of it
내가 처리할게
I will tell you
난 당신을 말할 것이다
fully understand
완전히 이해하다
Hi pretty girl
안녕 이쁜 소녀 야
How did you get your hand injured?
손은 어떻게 다쳤나요?
we are separated
우리는 헤어졌다
This is the so-called water of forgetfulness
이것이 소위 망각의 물이다.
This is for you
이건 널위한거야
her hand is hurt
그 사람 손이 다쳤어
Is it okay to give her wine?
그녀에게 와인을 줘도 괜찮을까요?
One cup of forgetful water per person
망각수 1인당 1컵
Can you forget it after drinking?
술을 마시고 나면 잊어버릴 수 있나요?
i really hope
나는 진정으로 원한다
Back to original
원본으로 돌아가기
The result is still the same
결과는 여전히 같습니다
Let's go talk somewhere else
다른데 가서 얘기하자
This is for you
이건 널위한거야
Anti-alcohol
항알코올
Thanks
감사해요
Thank you for staying in the hospital
병원에 머물러 주셔서 감사합니다
Stay with me for two days
이틀 동안 나와 함께 있어줘
Don't do this again next time
다음부터 이런 짓은 하지 마세요
I'm not always so lucky
나는 항상 그렇게 운이 좋은 것은 아니다
I didn't think much about it at the time
그 당시에는 그것에 대해 많이 생각하지 않았습니다.
I'm worried you'll get hurt
네가 다칠까봐 걱정돼
No matter how others hurt me
다른 사람들이 나에게 아무리 상처를 주더라도
it won't hurt me too much
별로 아프지 않을 거야
Their mission is mine
그들의 임무는 나의 것이다
That is
그건
Play a special game with you
당신과 함께 특별한 게임을 즐겨보세요
But our experience is real
하지만 우리의 경험은 진짜야
I can leave too
나도 떠날 수 있어
But I'm back to see you again
하지만 난 너를 다시 만나러 돌아왔어
in fact
사실은
That day at the casino
그날 카지노에서
I have thought about this problem
나는 이 문제에 대해 생각해 본 적이 있다.
i want to tell you
나는 당신에게 말하고 싶다
to be honest
솔직히 말하자면
if you really want to tell me
정말로 나에게 말하고 싶다면
the truth
진실
No need to gamble
도박을 할 필요가 없습니다
can decide
결정할 수 있다
but if i tell you
하지만 내가 너한테 말하면
perhaps
아마도
Accompany you to surrender
항복할 때까지 동행하라
I'm really afraid of going to jail
감옥에 가는 게 정말 무서워요
so
그래서
I used a bet
나는 내기를 사용했다
Help you make a decision
결정을 내리도록 도와주세요
I know it's cowardly
비겁한 짓이라는 걸 알아
Why are you a spy?
당신은 왜 스파이입니까?
My parents died young
부모님은 어렸을 때 돌아가셨어요.
And my family conditions are not good either.
그리고 우리 집안 형편도 좋지 않아요.
since childhood
어린 시절부터
My sister works part time
내 여동생은 아르바이트를 해
I am responsible for studying
나는 공부를 담당한다
until one day
언젠가까지
my colleague told me
내 동료가 나에게 말했어
play this game
이 게임을 해보세요
you can make a lot of money
당신은 많은 돈을 벌 수 있습니다
I'm curious
궁금해
so follow them
그러니 그들을 따라가세요
Play game together
함께 게임하기
Even on the day of the mission
미션 당일에도
come down
내려와
Get down immediately
즉시 내리세요
raise your hand
손 들어
put your hand in my sight
내 눈앞에 네 손을 올려봐
Get down immediately
즉시 내리세요
come down
내려와
All right
괜찮은
go out
나가
We received a report
우리는 보고서를 받았습니다
You are suspected of possessing illegal weapons
불법 무기를 소지한 혐의를 받고 있습니다.
What?
무엇?
it's out of the question
그건 말도 안 돼
open this box
이 상자를 열어봐
Open
열려 있는
I always
난 항상
explain it to them
그들에게 설명해보세요
I'm just playing games
난 그냥 게임을 하고 있어
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
Where did the gun come from?
총은 어디서 났나요?
But they just asked me
그런데 방금 나한테 물어보더라고.
Is the car mine?
차는 내꺼야?
We need to deliver the gun
총을 배달해야 해
No. 9772 Olympic Street
9772 올림픽 거리
This is the address
주소는 다음과 같습니다
The weird thing is
이상한 점은
the address they mentioned
그들이 언급한 주소
This is the mission of the game
이것이 게임의 미션이다
trading locations
거래 장소
I can only keep telling them
나는 그들에게 계속 말할 수 밖에 없다
it's just a game
이건 그냥 게임 일 뿐이야
I asked them
나는 그들에게 물었다.
They used my phone to check
그들은 내 전화를 사용하여 확인했습니다.
but on my phone
하지만 내 휴대전화에서는
in my phone
내 전화기에
she disappeared
그녀는 사라졌다
police told me
경찰이 나한테 말했어
People who receive this address
이 주소를 받는 사람들
I admit
나는 인정한다
I bought the weapons myself
무기는 내가 직접 샀다
on my phone
내 전화에
in my phone
내 전화기에
Record your contact information with him
그 사람과의 연락처를 기록해 두세요
All the evidence at the time
당시의 모든 증거
Refers
추천
Know
알다
i was cheated
나는 속았다
There must be something wrong with this game
이 게임에 뭔가 문제가 있는 게 틀림없어
i live in that room
나 그 방에 살아
in that room
그 방에서
I realized later
나중에 깨달았어요
The girl smuggled drugs
그 소녀는 마약을 밀수입했다
white girl killed
백인 여자가 죽었어요
black aunt
흑인 이모
He is a thieving criminal
그 사람은 도둑놈이에요
those days
그 시절
every day
매일
I dare not sleep
감히 잠을 못 자겠어
when i fall asleep
내가 잠들 때
I had a lot of nightmares
악몽을 많이 꿨어요
until one day,
어느 날까지,
The jailer told me
간수가 나에게 말했다.
It turns out someone recognized me.
누군가가 나를 알아본 것으로 나타났습니다.
I went crazy
나는 미쳤다
I'm jailbroken
나는 탈옥됐다
I do not want
하고 싶지 않다
Go back to that place.
그 곳으로 돌아가세요.
He asked me to call him Mr. Yu
유씨라고 불러달라고 하더군요
sit.
앉다.
I can help you get rid of the guilt
나는 당신이 죄책감을 없애도록 도울 수 있습니다
but there is a condition
하지만 조건이 있어요
any conditions
모든 조건
keep playing
계속 놀아
I can't play anymore
더 이상 놀 수 없어요
game let me
게임하자
in this case
이 경우
it seems
것 같다
you prefer prison
넌 감옥을 더 좋아해
Why did you involve me?
왜 나를 포함시켰나요?
We need your help
우리는 너의 도움이 필요해
What do you need me to do?
내가 무엇을 해야 합니까?
Go back to school and study hard
학교로 돌아가서 열심히 공부하세요
keep playing
계속 놀아
follow me
나를 따라와
a person who plays games
게임하는 사람
This is the second generation government
이게 2세대 정부다
This is the second time we've done this
우리가 이런 일을 한 것은 이번이 두 번째입니다
People we met at the hotel
호텔에서 만난 사람들
Of course someone will come to save him
물론 누군가가 그를 구하러 올 것이다.
but i'm different
하지만 난 달라
No one helped me at all
아무도 나를 전혀 도와주지 않았다
So then
그럼
I agree with that deal
나는 그 거래에 동의한다
as i expected
내가 예상했던 대로
after a while
잠시 후
Break all recognition
모든 인식을 깨뜨려라
He said he deliberately accused me
그 사람은 고의로 나를 비난했다고 하더군요
The way to communicate is to find hackers
소통의 길은 해커를 찾는 것
intentionally
의도적으로
My gun is in my car
내 총이 내 차에 있어요
exist
존재하다
Unknown status
알 수 없는 상태
it is placed inside
안쪽에 배치되어 있어요
Because there is not enough evidence
증거가 충분하지 않기 때문에
I was acquitted
나는 무죄를 선고받았다
I asked Mr. Yu
유씨에게 물어보니
who is he
그 사람은 누구입니까?
he tells me
그는 나에게 말한다
they are an information organization
그들은 정보 조직이다
They collected all the information
그들은 모든 정보를 수집했습니다
The name of the organization is "Night Mist"
조직 이름은 '밤의 안개'
The homework they sent me
그들이 나에게 보낸 숙제
this is a survey
이건 설문조사야
What kind of players can they develop into?
그들은 어떤 선수로 성장할 수 있나요?
Then he asked me to report
그랬더니 나보고 신고하라고 하더군요
I give them all the content
나는 그들에게 모든 콘텐츠를 제공합니다
Will choose night mist
나이트미스트를 선택하겠습니다
Some players will be selected
일부 플레이어가 선택됩니다.
He asked me to take them to the game
그는 나에게 그들을 경기에 데려가라고 요청했다
So I came to Tianhai
그래서 텐하이에 왔어요
according to their requirements
그들의 요구 사항에 따라
Who asked for them?
누가 요청했나요?
and become your partner
그리고 당신의 파트너가 되어주세요
At that time you were like
그 때 당신은 그랬어요
Like the straw that saved me
나를 구해준 지푸라기처럼
i have to catch you
난 당신을 잡아야 해요
Because I promised
약속했으니까
if they let you
그들이 당신을 허락한다면
Join the game
게임에 참여하세요
They won't take advantage of my family.
그들은 내 가족을 이용하지 않을 것입니다.
force
힘
Do anything
무엇이든 하세요
.then I can finish the game
.그럼 게임 끝낼 수 있겠네요
I'm leaving Jin Hye
나 진혜 떠난다
Do you believe what they say?
당신은 그들이 말하는 것을 믿습니까?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
I really don't want to go to jail
난 정말 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
I dare not resist
감히 저항하지 못해요
I don't believe them
나는 그들을 믿지 않는다
i can't believe you
나는 당신을 믿을 수 없다
You almost killed my father
당신은 내 아버지를 거의 죽일 뻔했어요
He also hurt his family
그는 가족에게도 상처를 입혔다
Is this your usual trick?
이게 평소의 트릭인가요?
sorry
죄송합니다
I really do not know
나는 정말로 모른다
they are taking advantage of your family
그들은 당신의 가족을 이용하고 있습니다
to threaten you
당신을 위협하기 위해
I regretted it very much at that moment
그 순간 정말 후회했어요
because I know
내가 알고 있기 때문에
Lonely
외로운
How terrible
얼마나 끔찍한가
I was just thinking
난 그냥 생각하고 있었어요
I can't leave you alone
난 당신을 혼자 둘 수 없어
alone
홀로
I'll let you face them alone
너 혼자 직면하게 해줄게
Because it's very dangerous
매우 위험하기 때문에
I don't want you to be
나는 당신이 그러는 걸 원하지 않아요
I am the second
나는 두 번째입니다
I'm scared every day
매일매일 겁이 나
helpless
어찌할 수 없는
and fear
그리고 두려움
so i'm back
그래서 내가 돌아왔어
I explain it all to you
나는 당신에게 모든 것을 설명합니다
not for
아닌
explain myself
나 자신을 설명하다
I just want to tell you
난 단지 당신에게 말하고 싶어
to be honest
솔직히 말하자면
That's it
그게 다야
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
future?
미래?
I know
알아요
us
우리를
we will complete our mission
우리는 우리의 임무를 완수할 것이다
you will face
당신은 직면하게 될 것이다
by the National Security Office
국가안보실에 의해
Is this the life you want?
이것이 당신이 원하는 삶인가요?
I only know
나만 알아요
i can't leave
난 떠날 수 없어
I can't leave you alone
난 당신을 혼자 둘 수 없어
There
거기
Although I
비록 나는
I work for Ye Wu
나는 Ye Wu에서 일해요
But I hate them as much as you do
하지만 나도 너만큼 그 사람들이 싫어
Because at the beginning
왜냐면 처음에는
at the beginning
처음에
probably now
아마 지금
how he hurt you
그 사람이 당신에게 얼마나 상처를 주었는지
Understood
이해했다
if
만약에
will you forgive me?
나를 용서해 주겠니?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
i need time to think
생각할 시간이 필요해
The same to you
너도 마찬가지야
think carefully
잘 생각 해봐
Do you give up?
포기하시나요?
hard freedom
힘든 자유
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
Ordinary people don't know
보통 사람들은 모르죠
Before going to Macau
마카오에 가기 전
Did Gao Tianyang tell you?
Gao Tianyang이 당신에게 말했습니까?
No
아니요
How did you know?
어떻게 알았나요?
tell me about the nurse station
간호사실에 대해 말해줘
Are you pretending?
당신은 척하고 있습니까?
I'm mad
내가 미친거야
I'm pretending here
난 여기서 그런 척을 하고 있어
Are all the people who come to the hospital sick?
병원에 오는 사람들은 다 아픈가요?
You've been stopped by spies
당신은 스파이에 의해 저지되었습니다
I'm still arrogant
난 아직도 거만한데
you are like this
당신은 이렇습니다
Go to Macau for me
나를 위해 마카오로 가세요
To save me from the fire
나를 불에서 구하려고
honestly
솔직히
I'm very impressed
나는 매우 감동했다
What does this mean to you?
이것이 당신에게 무엇을 의미합니까?
I am for the country
나는 국가를 위해
Do not think too much
깊은 생각 하지마
Understood
이해했다
seventh bed
일곱 번째 침대
Getting ready to clean the floor on the third floor
3층 바닥 청소 준비
OK
좋아요
Where did you buy the wheelchair?
휠체어는 어디서 구입하셨나요?
I rented it in the basement of the hospital
병원 지하에서 빌렸어요
I can walk by myself
혼자서 걸을 수 있어요
The doctor said
의사가 말했다.
I'm recovering well
잘 회복하고 있어요
I can be discharged from the hospital in two days
이틀이면 퇴원할 수 있어요
This is not a simple wheelchair
이것은 단순한 휠체어가 아닙니다.
This is my apology to Sister Shi
이건 시 자매님께 사과드립니다
and respect
그리고 존경한다
I believe
나는 믿는다
This is the curse you gave me
이건 네가 나에게 준 저주야
This is better
이게 낫다
Your feet look like this
발은 이렇게 생겼어요
Replacement goes to Macau
교체는 마카오로 갑니다
Isn't that all?
그게 다 아닌가요?
You are my own choice
당신은 나의 선택입니다
i must protect you
나는 당신을 보호해야합니다
besides it
게다가
I promised your brother
네 동생에게 약속했어
to protect you
당신을 보호하기 위해
it seems
것 같다
My brother is very important to you
내 동생은 당신에게 매우 중요합니다
Stop talking nonsense
말도 안되는 소리 그만해
let's talk about work
일에 대해 얘기하자
What did Yaoyao say?
야오야오가 뭐라고 말했어요?
Yaoyao said
야오야오가 말했다.
Players who have played games with it
그걸로 게임을 해본 플레이어들
I am playing game
나는 게임을 하고 있다
This is the second generation government
이게 2세대 정부다
Have you seen this hotel before
이 호텔을 본 적이 있나요?
Is his name Fang Lu?
그 사람 이름이 Fang Lu인가요?
Yes
예
This is it
이거 야
Fang Lu
팡 루
fully understand
완전히 이해하다
become
~이 되다
Can you
할 수 있나요
answer me a question
질문에 대답해줘
What?
무엇?
Do you think?
당신은 생각하십니까?
What Yaoyao said is true
야오야오의 말이 사실이다
what do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
Do you believe
당신은 믿습니까
What she said is true
그녀가 말한 것은 사실이다
except me
나 빼고
I trust your judgment more
나는 당신의 판단을 더 신뢰합니다
i can't answer you
나는 당신에게 대답할 수 없습니다
I need to investigate to make a judgment
조사해서 판단해야지
but we need
하지만 우리는 필요해
Continue to cooperate with Yaoyao
Yaoyao와 계속 협력
Investigate the details of Yaoyao
Yaoyao의 세부 사항을 조사하십시오
Especially her relationship with Fang Lu
특히 Fang Lu와의 관계
we must know
우리는 알아야 해
Fang Lu’s status in the game
Fang Lu의 게임 내 상태
Except Yaoyao
야오야오 제외
does he have
그 사람은 갖고 있어?
Any other contact details
기타 연락처 정보
or partner
또는 파트너
Are we partners?
우리는 파트너인가요?
Or our opponent?
아니면 우리의 상대?
Yes
예
This is it
이거 야
complicated
복잡한
say
말하다
What can't I ask?
내가 무엇을 물어볼 수 없나요?
become
~이 되다
tell me
말해 주세요
In the private world of workers
노동자들의 사적인 세계에서
In a world of private workers?
개인 노동자의 세계에서?
nature
자연
who has no feelings
감정이 없는 사람
but
하지만
hard to have
가지기 힘든
we don't care about anything
우리는 아무것도 신경 쓰지 않아
Because why แบก is not
왜 แบม이 아닌가?
This is the country's mission
이것이 국가의 사명이다
Know
알다
no matter what happens
무슨 일이 있어도
from
~에서
Can not accept
받아들일 수 없다
you did well
당신은 잘 했어요
honestly
솔직히
your performance
당신의 성과
better than i expected
내가 예상했던 것보다 더 좋아
if
만약에
I mean if
내 말은 만약에
What about Yaoyao?
야오야오는 어떻습니까?
Everything she said is true
그녀가 말한 모든 것은 사실이다
Already framed
이미 액자에 넣어져 있음
is forced
강요된다
But now I regret it
하지만 지금은 후회한다
Can she still be saved?
그녀는 아직 구원받을 수 있나요?
Do you still want to save her?
아직도 그녀를 구하고 싶나요?
I believe I can save someone
난 누군가를 구할 수 있다고 믿어
more important than arresting someone
누군가를 체포하는 것보다 더 중요한 것은
Did I say something wrong?
나 뭐 잘못 말했어?
Yes
예
I believe what you say
나는 당신이 말하는 것을 믿습니다
Very logical
매우 논리적
but you must remember
하지만 기억해야 해
maintain your image
이미지를 유지하세요
don't do anything
아무것도 하지 마세요
anything beyond your design
당신의 디자인을 넘어서는 무엇이든
other problems
다른 문제
We will help you solve it
우리는 당신이 그것을 해결하는 데 도움이 될 것입니다
As for Yaoyao
야오야오의 경우
what did i give you
내가 너에게 무엇을 주었니?
Must verify
확인해야 함
you must be conscious
당신은 의식이 있어야합니다
if you want to save her
그녀를 구하고 싶다면
She can't lie to you anymore
그녀는 더 이상 당신에게 거짓말을 할 수 없습니다
I remember
기억해
Didn't you delete your number?
전화번호 안 지웠어?
What is a fake corpse?
가짜 시체란 무엇인가?
things have changed
여러가지가 바뀌었다
Life is re-planned
인생은 다시 계획된다
almost
거의
allow
허용하다
I'll give you the tools
도구를 드릴게요
no need
필요 없음
all these external things
이 모든 외부적인 것들
I'm looking for you now
나는 지금 당신을 찾고 있어요
I have more important things
나에겐 더 중요한 일이 있다
What?
무엇?
Help me find someone
누군가를 찾도록 도와주세요
Are you looking for someone else?
다른 사람을 찾고 있나요?
My partner from the last game
지난 게임의 내 파트너
I need more information
더 많은 정보가 필요해요
any information
어떠한 정보
For example its calculation
예를 들어 계산
password
비밀번호
If I had her account password
내가 그 사람 계정 비밀번호를 갖고 있었다면
I still need you
난 아직도 당신이 필요해요
How did you get into her game?
그녀의 게임에 어떻게 참여하게 되었나요?
haven't discovered it yet
아직 발견하지 못했어요
therefore
그러므로
I will sell digital decompilers
디지털 디컴파일러를 판매하겠습니다
via her computer or mobile phone
그녀의 컴퓨터나 휴대폰을 통해
There is a game log
게임로그가 있어요
Why do I feel this way?
왜 이런 느낌이 들까요?
you can't fix it
넌 고칠 수 없어
Just want to sell me
그냥 나를 팔고 싶어
digital decoding program
디지털 디코딩 프로그램
I'll give you an idea
내가 당신에게 아이디어를 줄 것이다
I'm not forced to buy them
억지로 사지는 않아요
I can't write a program to decode that number
나는 그 숫자를 해독하는 프로그램을 작성할 수 없습니다
I do not need you
나는 당신이 필요 없습니다
You are very busy
당신은 매우 바쁘다
I tried it, it helped
해봤는데 도움이 됐어요
I trust you
나는 당신을 신뢰합니다
I will email you later
나중에 이메일로 보내드릴게요
OK
좋아요
I have no money
난 돈이 없다
he was first convicted
그는 처음으로 유죄 판결을 받았습니다
Do not make money
돈을 벌지 마십시오
Do I want your money?
내가 당신의 돈을 원하나요?
There is true love in the world
세상에는 진정한 사랑이 있다
give me a car
나에게 차를 줘
What
무엇
process
프로세스
I didn't tell her
나는 그녀에게 말하지 않았다
About our separation
우리의 이별에 대해
Understood
이해했다
sit
앉다
Is there any problem with Huitianhai?
Huitianhai에 문제가 있나요?
If you don't bother me there won't be a problem
네가 나를 괴롭히지 않는다면 문제는 없을 거야
You will adapt to your new identity
당신은 새로운 정체성에 적응할 것입니다
What is the new mission?
새로운 임무는 무엇인가요?
Working at Jihai Biological Group
Jihai Biological Group에서 근무
my father is there
내 아버지가 거기 계시다
correct
옳은
Didn't you promise me?
나한테 약속하지 않았어?
Don't get my father involved.
우리 아버지를 개입시키지 마세요.
If you enter
당신이 입력하면
You won't have anything to do with him
당신은 그 사람과 아무 관련이 없습니다
How could I not influence him?
내가 어떻게 그에게 영향을 미치지 않을 수 있겠는가?
So you must be careful
그러니까 조심해야 해
don't cause any trouble
문제를 일으키지 마세요
Do not disturb Mr. Huang
황 선생님을 방해하지 마세요
My father didn't run that company.
우리 아버지는 그 회사를 운영하지 않으셨어요.
I have no intention of entering
들어갈 생각은 없어
Enter
입력하다
nature
자연
I will give you time
시간을 줄게
With Mr. Huang
황씨와 함께
In addition to your major
전공 외에도
Enter the Internet section
인터넷 섹션으로 들어가세요
it's not difficult
어렵지 않아요
There is a Yaoyao who can help you
당신을 도와줄 야오야오가 있습니다
How did you apply for employment?
입사지원은 어떻게 하셨나요?
she has a great method
그 사람은 좋은 방법을 갖고 있어
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
What’s wrong with you
왜 그래?
What's up with her?
그녀에게 무슨 일이 있는 걸까요?
I have to ask you
물어볼 게 있어요
I gonna go see
보러 갈게